Minimum system Requirements:-

-Windows 7, 8, 10, 64 bits  (PC or Mac computers using Boot Camp).
-Any CPU (Intel i5/ i7/ Xeon recommended).
-Any GPU that is compatible with OpenGL 3.2. (integrated graphic cards Intel HD 4000 or above).


Steps to execute the project :-

1)goto required softwares-libraries folder and install all the softwares (viz AdobeAirInstaller,QuicktimeInstaller & WinVDIG_201).

2)In the same folder goto processing-1.5.1 and execute processing.exe. Now a folder named 'Processing' must be created in C:\Users\user_name\Documents.

3) Now copy 'libraries' folder to C:\Users\user_name\Documents\Processing.

4)Goto markers folder and print out markers ( or you may store it into a smartphone, but taking printouts is recommended). 

5)Ensure your webcam is working.

6)Goto project files and navigate to any three subfolders (viz. ads, Alphabets & interior) and execute the .pde file.

7) Click on run button.

8)Place any markers in front of the webcam and voila!

Note:-

1) Alphabets.pde users can stop/start rotation by a simple mouse click. Furthermore, users can also view the object from any angle by dragging mouse. Only alphabets A-I can be viewed,
   rest have been commented. You can view rest by removing comments.

2) In ads.pde users can pause/play video by simple mouse click.

3) interior.pde:  This is a demo project where users get to visualize the furniture at their home.Click to change the object. Use markers ‘A’ and ‘S’ for viewing furniture. Objects can be scaled up or down in size by pressing '↑' or '↓'.
